

ABOUT ME

With over 8 years of hands-on experience in the field, I have honed my skills in designing, developing, and maintaining .NET applications that meet and exceed client expectations. In addition to my technical proficiency, I am dedicated to staying abreast of the latest industry trends and advancements.

SKILL

ASP NET

NET CORE

MICROSERVICES

EF/EFCORE

AZURE SERVICE

SQL

NOSQL

WEB SERVICES API

AGILE/SCRUM

GIT/GITLAB

UNIT TESTING

MANAGEMENT

REACT JS

DONG **NGUYEN PHI**

SR. NET DEVELOPER/TEAM LEADER

CONTACT

- +84 77963 0574
- dong@open-vn.org
- Thoi Nhat Ward, District 12

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER 2015-2016

Finsom JSC

Finsom JSC is a financial technology startup, based in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. Our mission is to leverage

innovative technology to

improve people's lives, especially in the

finance sector.

Finsom's products is social lending platform to solve student loans problem in emerging markets.

Task

- Develop product new feature.
- Maintenance and management server.

- Technology Angular JS (1.0)
 - MongoDB
 - Golang

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER 2016-2019

Sorimachi VietNam

Task

- Develop new feature related based on client requirement.
- Optimizing query performance (SQL query).
- · Review code of junior members.
- Write test and testing with test-case and unit-test.
- Develop product's core APIs.
- Implement, customize product's UI.

< 10 members Team size

LANGUANGE



HOBBY

Badminton

Research new technology

Travel

Technology • Javascript/HTML/CSS/jQuery

C#, MVC 4

• MS SQL Server (query, store

procedure, ...)

SR BACK-END DEVELOPER 2019-2023

GlobalTech JSC

• Develop product's new feature. Task

• Develop Back-end core APIs.

• Implement VMware virtualization into product's feature.

• Training and review code for junior members in team.

• Contribute ideas for products.

• Research for new feature/new technology (as BA).

Team size < 10 members

Technology • VMware Virtualization suite/VCenter's APIs.

Net Core 3.1

• Net Framework 4.8

ASP Net

• GrapQL

MongoDB

• Angular/HTML5/SCSS/TypeScript

SR NET DEVELOPER 2023-Now

StepMedia Software

• Develop product's new feature. Task

• Maintain existing functions.

• Implement DB migration

requirement.

• Write and testing using unit test.

• Develop internal products/tools.

• Perform agile team tasks.

Team size < 20 members

Technology • Net 6, Net 8

ReactJS

· Azure services bus

Azure functions

• Entity Framework Core

MS SQL Server

• Postgres SQL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology 2010-2015 Ho Chi Minh City Pedagogical University